12fly.com.my 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy

“12FLY” provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of this mobile application (the “App”, and collectively with the Site, the "Services") about our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information.

**Changes**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site, and by email if you have provided us with your email address. The changes shall take effect after we post or otherwise notify you about the changes. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

**Your Consent**

By using the Services, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in Malaysia. If you reside outside the Malaysia, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to Malaysia, and processed and stored there under Malaysia privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in Malaysia.

**Information Collection**

Registration with us is optional. However, please keep in mind that you may not be able to use some of the features offered by the Services unless you register with us. When you register with us and use the Services, you provide information about yourself. Depending on how you use the Services, such information that you provide to us may include: (a) your name, email address, age (to comply with legal requirements), user name, password and other registration information; (b) your interaction with the Services and advertisements; (c) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us; (d) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (e) credit card information and (f) information you enter into our system when using the Services, such as contact information and project management information.

In addition, we may collect certain information that cannot be used to personally identify any user, and may be provided to third parties. Such non-personal data ordinarily includes aggregate, summary, or other usage data, and may include, by way of example, statistics regarding total users, information regarding types of Internet browsers used by users, and widget usage patterns. We also collect non-personal data about each users IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Services.

We do not access or store information that you have saved on your mobile device such as contacts and appointments. Although in order to provide the Services, our Applications may interact with some features on your mobile device, such as your calendar and e-mail applications, all processing occurs on the mobile device itself, and no information is transferred to 12FLY.

**Links; Third-Party Applications**

The Services may include links or otherwise allow you to access and submit information to third-party applications or sites. This Privacy Policy applies to the Services only. Any information you submit to linked sites or other applications will be subject to the privacy policies of those sites or applications, if any.

**Use of Information**

We may track usage data and user traffic patterns throughout our Site to improve the content of our Site and the quality of our service. We may use your information (a) to deliver the Services and features desired by you, (b) to improve our services to you, (c) to personalise content and offers that may be of interest to you, (d) to respond to your inquiries, and (e) to fullfil your request for products or services. 

We do not share personal identifying information collected on the Services, including email addresses, with third parties for their direct marketing or solicitation. We will use your contact information to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information or required notices. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 12fly uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of 12fly websites, and their website access preferences. 12fly visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 12fly's Services, with the drawback that certain features of our Services may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on the Services are delivered to users by our advertisers. We may from time-to-time use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on the Services. In the event we use such advertising networks on the Services, we will list such network here. Since our use of advertising networks may change form time-to-time, we encourage you to review this privacy policy periodically for changes. Advertisers and ad networks use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies on your browser to help present offers, better target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements by using data gathered on an anonymous basis over time and across their network of Web pages to determine the preference of their audiences. These cookies and web beacons do not collect any personal information from your computer, such as your e-mail address. The use of cookies and web beacons by advertisers and ad networks is subject to their own privacy policies. In the event we use advertising networks, you will have the opportunity to find out more about ad network providers and the choices you have about these technologies.

**Children**

We do not use the Services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [enquiry@12fly.com.my](mailto:enquiry@12fly.com.my). We will delete such information from our files.

**Acquisition**

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of 12FLY, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.

Managing Your Personal Data

In the event you desire to discontinue the Services and have your information removed from our systems, please send your request to [enquiry@12fly.com.my](mailto:enquiry@12fly.com.my).

**Security**

12fly is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We require physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. We limit access to personal information about you to authorised employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. Please be aware that, although we endeavour to provide reasonable security for information in our possession and control, no security system can prevent against all potential security breaches, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal data or non-personal data arising in connection with the theft thereof. Likewise, you are responsible for safeguarding the confidentiality of any usernames and passwords to the Services, and we bear no liability for access to, or use or disclosure of personal data if such access, use or disclosure arises in connection with the theft or disclosure (whether intentional or negligent) of such user's password.

**How to Contact 12FLY**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, or if you believe there are inaccuracies in your account information you may contact us as follows:

12FLY.COM.MY (Malaysian Harmony Tour & Travel Sdn Bhd)

Address: 21 Jalan Tung Shin, 50200 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Email: [enquiry@12fly.com.my](mailto:enquiry@12fly.com.my)
